[
    {
        "question": "What function would you use to convert a string to an int?",
        "answer": "the int function"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you access the first character of the string Python?",
        "answer": "use index 0 of the string python"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you check if a string contains only digits?",
        "answer": "use the string is digit method"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you check if a substring exists in a string?",
        "answer": "you can use the in operator the find method the index method or regular expression search"
    },
    {
        "question": "When using the plus operator to concatenate two strings, what needs to be considered?",
        "answer": "if you want spaces in between strings"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you convert a string to a list of words?",
        "answer": "use the split method"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you convert an integer to a string?",
        "answer": "using the string method"
    },
    {
        "question": "When declaring a string, what characters are used to enclose the string?",
        "answer": "single or double quotes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you get a character from an ASCII value?",
        "answer": "use the chr function"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you get the ASCII value of a character?",
        "answer": "use the ord function"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the strip() method?",
        "answer": "the strip method removes any spaces at the beginning or end of a string"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of using the plus sign between two strings you are printing?",
        "answer": "the two strings are placed side by side with no space between them"
    },
    {
        "question": "What function would you used with one = '1' and two = '2' to get output 3?",
        "answer": "the int function"
    },
    {
        "question": "What would you use to get a string to go to uppercase?",
        "answer": "use strings upper method"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happens if you attempt to apply the method lowercase to a string with numbers in it?",
        "answer": "the characters in the string are only changed to lowercase"
    },
    {
        "question": "Differentiate between name = 'Bob' and NAME = 'Bob'?",
        "answer": "there value will be the same, they may even occupy the same memory"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you get the memory location of a variable",
        "answer": "use the function id"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is a string a mutable or immutable object?",
        "answer": "immutable"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a variable name called that only uses capital letters?",
        "answer": "a constant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Yes or No. Is there any difference between the treatment of a constant and a variable in Python?",
        "answer": "no"
    },
    {
        "question": "Yes or no. Can we use reserved keywords as a variable name?",
        "answer": "no"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you create a string literal?",
        "answer": "by either using single or double quotes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is used at the beginning and end of multi-line strings?",
        "answer": "triple quotes or triple double quotes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you find the type of an object?",
        "answer": "use the type function"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the function used to capitalize strings?",
        "answer": "capitalize"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the function used to capitalize every first letter of each word in a string?",
        "answer": "title"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 'str' in the 'str.join()' method?",
        "answer": "it is the separator used between elements in the iterable"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you use the 'str.join()' method on a set, what will the results be?",
        "answer": "sets are unordered collections you cannot guarantee the resulting string"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you reverse a string?",
        "answer": "use slicing the reverse function or a loop"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does string.replace('old', 'new') do?",
        "answer": "it replaces all occurrences of the old string with the new string in a string"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is slicing strings?",
        "answer": "slicing strings allows the extraction of part of a string"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the difference between + and str.join() when combining strings?",
        "answer": "the plus operator does not have any way of separating strings join does"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of Python times three?",
        "answer": "the string python python python"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the value returned of len('Python')",
        "answer": "six"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you check if a string is a palindrome?",
        "answer": "reverse the string then compare it to the original string"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you convert a string to lowercase?",
        "answer": "use strings lower method"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does `max()` do when applied to a list of strings?",
        "answer": "it looks through the list and finds the string alphabetically to be last"
    }
]